A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Communications Office photographs, RG 20, SG 1 FA780
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Communications Office photographs, RG 20, SG 1
1959-1991
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA780
13.1 Cubic Feet 10 record storage boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 20 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Records arranged as received.
Scope and Contents
Contains slides, prints and other still images. Primarily documents activities in Brazil, Mexico and the Philippines. Images and associated correspondence also include selections made for use in several annual reports, newsletters, and select other publications and reports as well as images of staff, officers, trustees and events.
Photographs
- 1966 Newsletter, 1966 July-December (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1969 - 4th Quarterly (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1967 Newsletter, 1967 November-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Milwaukee Composers (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1972 Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Negative File Numbers (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 7)
- India - A Partnership (Box 1, Folder 8)
- MSA - Confidential (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Guatemala (Box 1, Folder 10)
- JDR 3rd Youth Award, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- JDR 3rd Youth Award - Renault A. Robinson (1978 Winner) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- RF Logo (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Staff and Program News, 1972 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Potato Blight - (Neiderhauser-Cobb), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CIAT Pictures, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- RF Trustees Meeting, Mexico, 1981 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Brazil - Bahia Site Visit, 1973 June (Box 1, Folder 18)
- IRRI - Life Magazine (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Sciences Seminar - Williamsburg, VA, 1979 November 18-21 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- JDR 3rd Youth Award - 1972 (Arts, Peggy Cooper) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Environment - Williams College - Williamstown, MA (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Mead, Margret (Box 1, Folder 23)
- RF Holiday Reception, 1980 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Musicians Conference, 1973 October (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Playwrights Conference, 1974 January (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Robinson, Nan S. (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Harrar, J. George - Cover of Memorial Book (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Philippines - IRRI - Prints (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Philippines - IRRI - Chromes (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Philippines - IRRI - Chromes, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Philippines - IRRI - Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Philippines - IRRI - Chromes (by Sterling Wortman) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Philippines - IRRI - Black and White prints of Chromes, 1975 November (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Brazil - Agriculture and Business Program - Salvador (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Brazil - Kumm, Henry W. - MosquitAerial Trap (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Thailand - Floating Rice (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Turkey - Agriculture - Wright, Bill C. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- RF Holiday Reception - Dec. 20, 1979 (images 1-30) - Images Used In Reception Brochure, 1979 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- RF Holiday Reception - Dec. 20, 1979 (images 31-61) - Images Used in Reception Brochure, 1979 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Images Not Used in Reception Brochure (Box 1, Folder 41-42)
- Vance, Cyrus (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Volcker, Paul A. (Box 2, Folder 44)
- RFI - Vol. 2, No. 1 - August 1974 (Harrar, Knowles and Rusk), 1974 August (Box 2, Folder 45)
- King, Edith E. (Box 2, Folder 46)
- The I-90 Dispute (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Warren, Kenneth S. (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Wellhausen, Edwin J. (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Weir, John M. (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Wernimont, Kenneth (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Warton, Clifton R., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Willrich, Mason (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Wolfensohn, James D. (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Wolling, Frank (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Wortman, Sterling (Box 2, Folder 56-57)
- Wright, Christopher (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Williams, Bruce (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Art Projects, 1988 Fall (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Argentina - Poverty - Buenos Aires (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Brazil - Education for Development - Bahia, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Brazil - Agriculture and Business Program (Box 2, Folder 63)
- China - Peking Hotel Reception, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- CIMMYT Agreement Signing, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Jackson, Ben (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Knowles, John H. - In China (Box 2, Folder 67)
- JDR 3rd Youth Award - Cobbs, Lisa, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Merci Aux Americains Poster (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Mexico- 2x2 Negatives (with Prints) (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Mexico- Pueblo Project (CIMMYT) (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Mexico - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Richardson, Ralph W. Jr. (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Seitz, Fredrick (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Smith, Charles H. (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Todaro, Michael P. (Box 2, Folder 76)
- West, Robert L. (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Wray, Joseph D. (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Bronte, D. Lydia (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Colton, Joel (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Fischelis, Robert L. (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Gilpatric, Chadbourne (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Heineman, Ben W. (Box 2, Folder 83)
- House, Leland R. (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Jackson, Elmore (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Kerr, Clark (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Hayes, Guy S. (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Houghton, Arthur A. Jr. (Box 2, Folder 88)
- July, Robert W. (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Kirschner, Leo (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Winikoff, Beverly (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Knowles, John H. (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Kumm, Henry W. (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Lleras Camarg, Alberto (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Allen, Jane (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Allen, Le Roy R. (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Anderson, Richmond K. (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Arnold, Virginia (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Baird, Guy B. (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Beachell, Henry M. (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Bell. Phillip W. (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Biringer, Roger (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Bourne, LeF. (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Bradley, William L. (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Bugher, John C. (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Coggeshall, Lowell T. (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Compton, Boyd R. (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Crawford, Robert W. (Box 2, Folder 110)
- DeVinney. Leland C. (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Dickey, John S. (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Dillon, Douglas (Box 2, Folder 113)
- French Tuberculosis Poster (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Oceanic Institute - Fish Chromes (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Humanities Conference - Change Magazine (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Italy - Bellagio (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Mexico - Chapingo (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Connell, Elizabeth B. (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Mauldin, W, Parker (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Chile - Infant Mortality (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Anderson, Bernard E. (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Anderson, R. Glenn (Box 3, Folder 123)
- APP, Alva, A (Box 3, Folder 124)
- Andrews, Lowry B. (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Arthurs, Alberta (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Barnes, Allan C. (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Black, Joseph E. (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Blumenthal, W. Michael (Box 3, Folder 129)
- Borlaug, Norman E. (Box 3, Folder 130-134)
- Bradfield, Richard (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Bronte, Lydia (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Bookmyer, Joseph R. (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Chandler, Robert F., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Coleman, James S. (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Colton, Joel (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Connell, Elizibeth B. (Box 3, Folder 141)
- Cummings, Ralph W., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 142)
- Cummings, Ralph W., Sr. (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Daunys, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Davidson, Ralph K. (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Dayton, Kenneth (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Deagle, Edwin A. (Box 3, Folder 147)
- DeVinney, Leland C. (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Dinning, James S. (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Fletcher, James Chipman (Box 3, Folder 150)
- Frye, Theodore R. (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Gallegos, Herman E. (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Grant, Ulysses J. (Box 3, Folder 153)
- Gregg, Lucien A. (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Gray, Clarence C., III (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Halstead, Scott B. (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Hardin, Cliford M. (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Harrar, J. George (Box 3, Folder 158-160)
- Heaton, Herbert (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Hayes, Guy S. (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Hess, J. William (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Jennings, Peter (Box 3, Folder 165)
- Jensen, James H. (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Johnson, James E. (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Jordan, Vernon E. (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. (Box 4, Folder 169)
- JDR, Sr. (Box 4, Folder 170)
- Index (Box 4, Folder 171)
- Post Renovation Pictures - Negatives (Box 4, Folder 172)
- Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 4, Folder 173)
- Williams, Bruce (Box 4, Folder 174)
- Taylor, Billy (Box 4, Folder 175)
- Fletcher, James C. (Box 4, Folder 176)
- Hess, J. William - RF Archivist (Box 4, Folder 177)
- Kritz, Mary (Box 4, Folder 178)
- Colton, Joel (Box 4, Folder 179)
- Davidson, R.K. (Box 4, Folder 180)
- Richardson, Ralph W., Jr. (Box 4, Folder 181)
- Horsefall, Dr. James G. (Box 4, Folder 182)
- Rockefeller, Jay (Box 4, Folder 183)
- Willrich, Mason (Box 4, Folder 184)
- Grant, James P. (Box 4, Folder 185)
- Warren, Kenneth (Box 4, Folder 186)
- Sheldon, Eleanor (Box 4, Folder 187)
- Mella, M (Box 4, Folder 188)
- Country Music (Box 4, Folder 189)
- 1978 Piano Competition - Concert Hall, JFK Center (Box 4, Folder 190)
- 1977 JDR 3rd Youth Award - Hilary Ng'weno (Box 4, Folder 191)
- 1979 JDR 3rd Youth Award - Lisa Cobbs (Box 4, Folder 192)
- 1978 JDR 3rd Youth Award - Renault Robinson (Box 4, Folder 193)
- Fisheries (Box 4, Folder 194)
- International Center for Living Aquatic Resources (ICLARM) - Fish (Box 4, Folder 195)
- Killer Bee (Box 4, Folder 196)
- IRRI - Rickerby, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 197)
- Stifel, L. D. (China) (Box 4, Folder 198)
- Small Farmers (Box 4, Folder 199)
- Youth Unemployment (Box 4, Folder 200)
- Population (Box 4, Folder 201)
- China Agriculture, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 202)
- Health Services (Box 5, Folder 203-204)
- Philippines - IRRI (Box 5, Folder 205)
- China (Box 5, Folder 206-207)
- Pakistan - Wheat Harvest (Box 5, Folder 208)
- Video Art (Box 5, Folder 209-211)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Outtakes, 1980 April (Box 5, Folder 212-213)
- Hastings Center (Box 5, Folder 214-215)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 6 (Box 5, Folder 216)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 7 (Box 5, Folder 217)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 8 (Box 5, Folder 218)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 9 (Box 5, Folder 219)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 10 - Duck Feeding (Box 5, Folder 220)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 11 (Box 5, Folder 221)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 12 (Box 5, Folder 222)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 13 (Box 5, Folder 223)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 14 - Rice Harvest (Box 5, Folder 224)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 15 (Box 5, Folder 225)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 16 (Box 5, Folder 226)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 17 (Box 5, Folder 227)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 18 (Box 5, Folder 228)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 19 (Box 5, Folder 229)
- Philippines - Los Banos - Edited - R.F. 20 - Rice (Box 5, Folder 230)
- Mexico - CIMMYT Take (Box 6, Folder 231)
- Mexico - Triticale, Wheat (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Mexico - Experimental Fields (Box 6, Folder 233)
- Mexico - Lab Interior (Box 6, Folder 234)
- Mexico - Professopnal Staff (Box 6, Folder 235)
- Mexico - Puebla Project (Box 6, Folder 236)
- Mexico - Stem Rust (Box 6, Folder 237)
- Mexico - CIMMYT (Box 6, Folder 238)
- Mexico - CIMMYT - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 239)
- Mexico - CIMMYT - 1974 - Spraque, Ernest W. (Box 6, Folder 240)
- Mexico - Prints Used in CIMMYT Book (Box 6, Folder 241)
- Mexico - El Batan (Box 6, Folder 242)
- Mexico - Training Maize + EJW (Box 6, Folder 243)
- Mexico - 1970 - Borlaug, N.E. (Box 6, Folder 244-245)
- Sterling Wortman - China Trip, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 246)
- Columbia, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 247)
- Columbia - The Llanos (Box 6, Folder 248)
- Guatemala, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 249)
- Guatemala - 1976 - Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 250)
- Indonesia - Village Nutrition Program (Box 6, Folder 251`)
- Kenya - ILRAD (Box 6, Folder 252-253)
- Nigeria - Badeku, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 254)
- Bangladesh - IRRI (Box 6, Folder 255-256)
- IRRI - 1974 - Massagana 99 (Box 6, Folder 257)
- The Sahel (Box 6, Folder 258-259)
- Health Sciences (Box 6, Folder 260)
- Family Business (Box 6, Folder 261)
- Rockefeller Archive Center, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 262)
- 1977 Visiting Research Fellows (RAC) (Box 6, Folder 263)
- Bronte, D. Lydia - New York (Box 6, Folder 264)
- Davidson, Ralph K. - New York, 1975 August (Box 6, Folder 265)
- Lyman, Richard W. (Box 6, Folder 266)
- Arts (Box 7, Folder 267)
- Lichtenstein, Harvey (Box 7, Folder 268)
- 1991 Annual Report Cover Art (Box 7, Folder 269)
- For Children's Sake (Box 7, Folder 270)
- Musoke, Theresa (Box 7, Folder 271)
- Downs, Hugh - Comer, James (Box 7, Folder 272)
- Contact Sheets by Photographer JoAnne Savio (Box 7, Folder 273)
- Norplant, Dr. Mati Kenya (Box 7, Folder 274)
- Seaweed Farming - Tanzania (Box 7, Folder 275)
- Bellagio (Box 7, Folder 276)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - A (Box 7, Folder 277)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - B (Box 7, Folder 278)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - C (Box 7, Folder 279)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - D-E (Box 7, Folder 280)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - F-G (Box 7, Folder 281)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - H (Box 7, Folder 282)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - J (Box 7, Folder 283)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - K (Box 7, Folder 284)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - L (Box 7, Folder 285)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - M (Box 7, Folder 286)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - N-O (Box 7, Folder 287)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - P-Q (Box 7, Folder 288)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - R (Box 7, Folder 289)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - S (Box 7, Folder 290)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - T (Box 7, Folder 291)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - U-V-W (Box 7, Folder 292)
- Support Staff - Program Associates - X-Y-Z (Box 7, Folder 293)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - A-F, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 294)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - G, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 295)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - H-L, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 296)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - M-Q, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 297)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - R, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 298)
- Officers, Managers, Assoc. Directors, Field Staff - S-Z, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 299)
- Trustees - A-J (Box 7, Folder 300)
- Trustees - K-Z (Box 7, Folder 301)
- Population P1 Chilean Birth Control (Box 7, Folder 302)
- Population P2 India (Box 7, Folder 303)
- Population P3 Dr. Helen Gideon at Harvard (Box 7, Folder 304)
- Population P4 Dr. Benjamin Vielat Santiago (Box 7, Folder 305)
- Population P5 Frank Notetein, Population Control (Box 7, Folder 306)
- Population P6 Claude A. Villee (Box 7, Folder 307)
- Population P7 Mexico (Box 7, Folder 308)
- Population P8 Birth Control in Brazil (Box 7, Folder 309)
- Population P9 Birth Control in Argentina (Box 7, Folder 310)
- Population P10 Jan Lippes (Box 7, Folder 311)
- Population P11 Ansley Coale (Box 7, Folder 312)
- Population P12 Dr. George Corner (Box 7, Folder 313)
- Population P13 University of North Carolina Population Center (Box 7, Folder 314)
- Population P14 Chicago Medical School (Box 7, Folder 315)
- Population P15 Cornell Medical School (Box 7, Folder 316)
- Population P16 Western Reserve University (Box 7, Folder 317)
- Population P17 Baylor University Family Planning (Box 7, Folder 318)
- Population P18 Louisiana Family Planning (Box 7, Folder 319)
- Population P19 University of Washington Medical School (Box 7, Folder 320)
- Population P20 Heceteppe, Turkey - Family Planning (Box 7, Folder 321)
- Population P21 Bernard Berelson -Population Council (Box 7, Folder 322)
- Population P22 AlvarGarcia - Pena (Box 7, Folder 323)
- Population P23 University of Mississippi Medical School (Box 7, Folder 324)
- Population P24 Dr. Roy Greep (Box 7, Folder 325)
- Population P25 Dr. Saul Gusberg (Box 7, Folder 326)
- Population P26 Dr. Luigi Mestroianni (Box 7, Folder 327)
- Population P27 Alfred Moran (Box 7, Folder 328)
- Population P28 Dr. Louis Hellman (Box 7, Folder 329)
- Population P29 Marc Nerlove (Box 7, Folder 330)
- Population P30 Ryan Reproductive Biology (Box 7, Folder 331)
- Population P31 Dr. Donald P. Swartz (Box 7, Folder 332)
- Population P32 Professor Gustav Ranis (Box 7, Folder 333)
- Population P33 Mrs. Lorraine Cleveland (Box 7, Folder 334)
- Population P34 Dr. David Hamilton (Box 7, Folder 335)
- Population P35 Professor David Glass (Box 7, Folder 336)
- Population P36 University of Michigan Population Studies Center (Box 7, Folder 337)
- Population P37 Dr. Andre Hellegers (Box 7, Folder 338)
- Population P38 Mississippi Delta Family Planning (Box 7, Folder 339)
- Population P39 Dr. John B. Wyon (Box 7, Folder 340)
- Population P40 Princeton University (Box 7, Folder 341)
- Population P41 Dr. Ronald Pion (Box 7, Folder 342)
- Population P42 Dr. Alan F. Gultmacher (Box 7, Folder 343)
- Population P43 Victor Uruidi (Box 7, Folder 344)
- Population P44 Dr. Bernard Berdson and Dr. Howard Taylor (Box 7, Folder 345)
- Population P45 Dr Stanley Bennett (Box 7, Folder 346)
- L. D. Stifel - Boat Ride, 1985 August 12 (Box 8, Folder 347)
- Dr. Sprague, Suwan Farm, Thailand (Box 8, Folder 348)
- RF 75th Anniversary (Box 8, Folder 349-353)
- Puerto Penasco - Plastic Greenhouses (Box 8, Folder 354)
- IRRI - Arial View (Box 8, Folder 355)
- Turkey (Box 8, Folder 356)
- Health and Family Planning - Cali and Candelaira, Columbia (Box 8, Folder 357)
- IR 8 (Box 8, Folder 358)
- Drought Plants (Box 8, Folder 359)
- IR 8 Rice Fields (Box 8, Folder 360)
- 30 Years of World Agriculture - 1971 Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 361)
- Norman E. Borlaug - Conquest of Hunger - Mexico, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 362)
- 150th Anniversary Event (Box 8, Folder 363)
- Mexico - Wheat Farmers (Box 8, Folder 364)
- Mexico - CIMMYT Near East Trainees (Box 8, Folder 365)
- Mexico - Triticale (Box 8, Folder 366)
- Thailand - Rural Health, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 367)
- Virginia Assemblies (Box 8, Folder 368)
- Philippine Terraces (Box 8, Folder 369)
- Mexico - CIMMYT Board Meeting (Box 8, Folder 370)
- Mexico - Field Day - Celaya (Box 8, Folder 371)
- Wheat - General (Box 8, Folder 372)
- Kimball, Lindsley F. (Box 8, Folder 373)
- Officers? Photos Book (Box 8, Folder 374)
- Schistosomiasis (Box 8, Folder 375)
- CIAT (Box 8, Folder 376)
- DELTA-MACE (Mississippi Action for Community Education) (Box 8, Folder 377)
- 1962 2nd Quarterly - Arts (Box 8, Folder 378)
- 1968 3rd Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 379)
- 1968 1st Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 380)
- 1967 Newsletter, 1967 January-June (Box 8, Folder 381)
- 1968 2nd Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 382)
- 1966 Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 383)
- 1964 4th Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 384)
- 1966 Newsletter, 1966 January-June (Box 8, Folder 385)
- 1967 Newsletter, 1967 July-October (Box 8, Folder 386)
- 1968 Newsletter, 1968 August-December (Box 8, Folder 387)
- 1971 Newsletter, 1971 July-August (Box 8, Folder 388)
- Mexico - Historical Interest (Box 8, Folder 389)
- Mexico, 1966 October (Box 8, Folder 390)
- 1967 - 3rd Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 391)
- 1971 Newsletter - Staff Photos, 1971 September-October (Box 9, Folder 392)
- 1971 Newsletter, 1971 November-December (Box 9, Folder 393)
- 1965 Arts Report (Box 9, Folder 394)
- 1970 November-December (Box 9, Folder 395)
- 1970 Newsletter, 1970 March-April (Box 9, Folder 396)
- 1971 Newsletter, 1971 March-April (Box 9, Folder 397)
- St. Lucia - Schistosomiasis Control Project (Box 9, Folder 398)
- Images Used By The Foundation News (Box 9, Folder 399)
- Belem Virus Laboratory (Box 9, Folder 400)
- Mexico - Shipping Wheat (Box 9, Folder 401)
- Mexico (Box 9, Folder 402)
- 1965 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 403)
- IRRI (Box 9, Folder 404-406)
- Ecuador - Conquest of Hunger, 1967 July (Box 9, Folder 407)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 408)
- Abu-Dhaki (Box 9, Folder 409)
- Agriculture Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 410)
- Rice, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 411)
- 1970 Newsletter, 1970 May-June (Box 9, Folder 412)
- 1968 Newsletter, 1968 January-May (Box 9, Folder 413)
- 1971 Newsletter, 1971 September-October (Box 9, Folder 414)
- 1971 Newsletter, 1971 January-February (Box 9, Folder 415)
- 1970 Newsletter, 1970 July-October (Box 9, Folder 416)
- 1969 Newsletter, 1969 August-December (Box 9, Folder 417)
- CIAT - Aerial Photos (Box 9, Folder 418)
- India - Famine (Box 9, Folder 419)
- India (Box 9, Folder 420)
- Seventh Annual Inter Asian Corn Workshop - Los Banos, Philippines, 1971 January (Box 9, Folder 421)
- Urban Migration - Latin America, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 422)
- CIMMYT - High Lysine Corn (Box 9, Folder 423)
- Thailand - Floating Rice, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 424)
- Colombia (Box 9, Folder 425-426)
- Borlaug (Box 9, Folder 427)
- 1966 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 428-429)
- Freund, Gerald (Box 9, Folder 430)
- Pakistan (Box 9, Folder 431)
- Pakistan - (Borlaug and Stakman), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 432)
- Potato Blight (Box 9, Folder 433)
- Honduras - Pan American School of Agriculture (Box 9, Folder 434)
- Michigan - East Lansing Lakes, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 435)
- Newsletter, 1967 January (Box 9, Folder 436)
- 1967 - Fourth Quaterly (Box 9, Folder 437)
- 1968 - First Quaterly (Box 9, Folder 438)
- 1968 - Fourth Quaterly (Box 9, Folder 439)
- Newsletter, 1969 January-July (Box 9, Folder 440)
- Westerberg, Nils J. (Box 9, Folder 441)
- Wood, Peter H. (Box 9, Folder 442)
- Gibler, John W (Box 10, Folder 443)
- Goheen, Robert F. (Box 10, Folder 444)
- Grant, John B. (Box 10, Folder 445)
- Greenfieldt, John H. (Box 10, Folder 446)
- Gregg, Alan (Box 10, Folder 447)
- Grevers, John H. (Box 10, Folder 448)
- Hardin, Charles M. (Box 10, Folder 449)
- Harrison, John P. (Box 10, Folder 450)
- Lloyd, Norman (Box 10, Folder 451)
- Maier, John (Box 10, Folder 452)
- Morison, Robert S. (Box 10, Folder 453)
- Paine, Janet M. (Box 10, Folder 454)
- Parker, Dorothy (Box 10, Folder 455)
- Peck, Marshall (Box 10, Folder 456)
- Perry, Jesse P., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 457)
- Peterson, Osler L. (Box 10, Folder 458)
- Novak, Michael (Box 10, Folder 459)
- Raun, Ned S. (Box 10, Folder 460)
- Renfro, Bobby L. (Box 10, Folder 461)
- Scott, Virgil C. (Box 10, Folder 462)
- Smith, J. Kellum, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 463)
- Steel, Row S. (Box 10, Folder 464)
- Theiler, Max (Box 10, Folder 465)
- Thomas Robert M. (Box 10, Folder 466)
- Thompson, Kenneth W. (Box 10, Folder 467)
- Vance, Cyrus R. (Box 10, Folder 468)
- Watson, Robert B. (Box 10, Folder 469)
- Wernimont, Kenneth (Box 10, Folder 470)
- Borlaug - Alternative Prints and Negatives (Box 10, Folder 471)
- Philippines (Box 10, Folder 472)
- IRRI, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 473)
- Negatives, 1987 June 22 (Box 10, Folder 474)
- Negatives, 1987 July 1 (Box 10, Folder 475)
- Negatives, 1987 June 19 (Box 10, Folder 476)
- Negatives, 1986 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 477)
- Negatives, 1988 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 478)
- Negatives, 1986 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 479)
- Negatives, 1985 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 480)
- Negatives, 1986 February 12 (Box 10, Folder 481)
- Negatives, 1986 March 7 (Box 10, Folder 482)
- Negatives, 1987 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 483)
- Negatives, 1988 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 484)
- Negatives, 1988 June 28 (Box 10, Folder 485)
- Negatives, 1988 August 21 (Box 10, Folder 486)
- Negatives, 1988 November 15 (Box 10, Folder 487)
- Italy - Bellagio - Landscape (Box 10, Folder 488)
- Italy - Bellagio - Scholars and Conferences (Box 10, Folder 489)
- Italy - Bellagio - Landscape and Archetecture (Box 10, Folder 490)
- Italy - Bellagio - Color Prints (Box 10, Folder 491)